Kotschnig, Walter Maria; Papers ger053
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Correspondence, 1927-1984; 2; 1402 folders
  - Correspondence of Walter M. Kotschnig during his years with the Department of State and the United Nations, 1937-1977; 1948-1972; 2.7; 585 folders
    - Allan, Warde B., 1953; 2 items (Box 6 (2-Correspondence), Folder 37)
    - Allen, Ethan P., 1954; 2 items (Box 6 (2-Correspondence), Folder 38)
    - Allen, Mark, 1970; 2 items (Box 6 (2-Correspondence), Folder 39)
    - Altmeyer, Arthur J., 1948; 1 item (Box 6 (2-Correspondence), Folder 40)
    - American Association for the United Nations, 1949; 1 item (Box 6 (2-Correspondence), Folder 41)
    - Andemicael, Berhanykun, 1977; 1 item (Box 6 (2-Correspondence), Folder 42)
    - Andrews, Elizabeth Peterson (Pete), 1969; 4 items (Box 6 (2-Correspondence), Folder 43)
    - Anslinger, Harry J., 1966-1967; 3 items (Box 6 (2-Correspondence), Folder 44)
    - Archibald, Charles H., 1968; 3 items (Box 6 (2-Correspondence), Folder 45)
    - Arnesen, Ragnar (United Nations Fund for Drug Abuse Control), 1971-1973; 20 items (Box 6 (2-Correspondence), Folder 46)
    - Ascher, Charles S., 1952-1972; 7 items (Box 6 (2-Correspondence), Folder 47)
    - Atlas, Lanny (Mrs. Martin), 1965; 2 items (Box 6 (2-Correspondence), Folder 48)
    - Ayusawa, Iwao F., 1949-1950; 3 items (Box 6 (2-Correspondence), Folder 49)
    - Babbott, Frank L. Jr., 1965; 1 item (Box 6 (2-Correspondence), Folder 50)
    - Baillie, Hugh, 1952; 1 item (Box 6 (2-Correspondence), Folder 51)
    - Baker, George Pierce, 1949; 3 items (Box 6 (2-Correspondence), Folder 52)
    - Baker, John C., 1953-1978; 19 items (Box 6 (2-Correspondence), Folder 53)
    - Baldanza, Stephen, 1951; 1963; 4 items (Box 6 (2-Correspondence), Folder 54)
    - Baldwin, Roger, 1953; 2 items (Box 6 (2-Correspondence), Folder 55)
    - Balgooyen, H. W., 1953; 1 item (Box 6 (2-Correspondence), Folder 56)
    - Bandoni, Norma, 1965; 2 items (Box 6 (2-Correspondence), Folder 57)
    - Barber, Willard F., 1949-1951; 3 items (Box 6 (2-Correspondence), Folder 58)
    - Barnes, Roswell P., 1946; 1 item (Box 6 (2-Correspondence), Folder 59)
    - Batson, Douglas N., 1966; 1 item (Box 6 (2-Correspondence), Folder 60)
    - BBC-tv, 1971; 1 item (Box 6 (2-Correspondence), Folder 61)
    - Beaven, Marion, 1972; 1 item (Box 6 (2-Correspondence), Folder 62)
    - Belcher, Marjorie S., 1968; 4 items (Box 6 (2-Correspondence), Folder 63)
    - Bell, Kathleen, 1975; Undated; 8 items (Box 6 (2-Correspondence), Folder 64)
    - Bellanger, Claude, 1950; 2 items (Box 6 (2-Correspondence), Folder 65)
    - Benton, William, 1947-1949; 39 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 1)
    - Rusk, Dean, Undated (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 1)
    - Benton, William, 1950-1957; 66 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 2)
    - Benton, William, 1965-1969; 87 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 3)
    - Luce, Clare Booth, Undated (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 3)
    - Benton, William, 1970-1973; 41 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 4)
    - Benton, Helen, 1973; 3 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 5)
    - Bergstrom, Donald R., 1971; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 6)
    - Berman, Philip I., 1967; 3 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 7)
    - Berner, T. Roland, 1972; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 8)
    - Bernstein, Meyer, 1968; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 9)
    - Bhanumas, Nitya, 1972; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 10)
    - Bigge, George E., 1953; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 11)
    - Binder, Carroll, 1951-1952; 9 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 12)
    - Bingham, Jack, Undated; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 13)
    - Birckhead, John T., 1969; 3 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 14)
    - Bitker, Bruno V., 1965; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 15)
    - Black, Cy E., 1950; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 16)
    - Blaisdell, Donald C., 1952; 3 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 17)
    - Blaisdell, Thomas C. Jr., 1951-1966; 5 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 18)
    - Blankfort, Henry, 1944; 8 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 19)
    - Blau, Clarence, 1971; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 20)
    - Block, Herbert, 1966; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 21)
    - Bock, Oscar F., 1949; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 22)
    - Bodet, Jaime Torres, 1950; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 23)
    - Bolton, Frances P., 1950-1951; 3 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 24)
    - Bonsal, 1950; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 25)
    - Boothby, E. B., 1949; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 26)
    - Boudreau, F. G., 1953; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 27)
    - Bourquin, Jacques E., 1949-1950; 5 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 28)
    - Bowditch, Richard L., 1953; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 29)
    - Bower, Molly, 1954; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 30)
    - Bowers, Claude G., 1951; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 31)
    - Bowles, Chester (Chet), 1965; 10 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 32)
    - Bowman, Raymond T., 1968; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 33)
    - Boyd, Roland, 1967; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 34)
    - Branscomb, Harvie, 1964-1965; 3 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 35)
    - Briggs, Ellis O., 1951; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 36)
    - Broadley, Sir Herbert, 1965-1966; 6 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 37)
    - Brohi, Allah Bukhsh K., 1950; 1965; 3 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 38)
    - The Brookings Institution (Robert Hartley, Robert Calkins), 1950-1958; 30 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 39)
    - Brown, Robert L., 1969; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 40)
    - Brown, Winthrop G., 1965; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 41)
    - Bunker, Carol & Ellsworth, Undated; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 42)
    - Bunting, Earl, 1949; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 43)
    - Burke, Edmund Jr., 1966; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 44)
    - Burnett, Philip M., 1950; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 45)
    - Bush, George, 1971-1972; 10 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 46)
    - Bushwaller, Regina, 1950; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 47)
    - Byfield, Robert S., 1953; 3 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 48)
    - Byrd, Harry F., 1951; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 49)
    - Byrne, Patricia, 1970; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 50)
    - Calderwood, Howard B., 1967; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 51)
    - Cameron, Pearl, 1968; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 52)
    - Caranicas, Costa P., 1970; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 53)
    - Carey, John, 1968; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 54)
    - Cates, John M. Jr., 1968-1975; 7 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 55)
    - Chafee, Z. Jr., 1948; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 56)
    - Cheever, Daniel S., 1966; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 57)
    - Christensen, Ronald A., 1971; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 58)
    - Clarke, Walter, 1949; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 59)
    - Cleveland, Harlan, 1963-1969; 5 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 60)
    - Cohen, Myer, 1965; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 61)
    - Cohn, Peter A., 1972; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 62)
    - Cohrssen, John J., 1972; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 63)
    - Compton, Arthur A., 1949-1950; 4 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 64)
    - Cooper, John Sherman, 1956; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 65)
    - Cordier, Andrew, 1965-1966; 4 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 66)
    - Cortney, Philip, 1951; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 67)
    - Cory, Robert H., 1970; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 68)
    - Cowell, F. R. (Dick), 1970; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 69)
    - Cox, Henry B., 1971; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 70)
    - Cox, Oscar, 1949; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 71)
    - Crawford, Morris H., 1970; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 72)
    - Crawford, William A., 1965; 3 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 73)
    - Daes, Erica-Irene A., 1970-1971; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 74)
    - Daniels, Jonathan, 1949; 7 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 75)
    - Darchambeau, Valère, 1950; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 76)
    - Dauer, Barbara, 1972; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 77)
    - Davidson, George, 1951-1972; 14 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 78)
    - Davies, Thurston J., 1949; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 79)
    - Davis, Emily C., 1952; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 80)
    - Davis, Lea (Mrs. Gary), Undated; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 81)
    - Davis, Nathaniel, 1966-1967; 3 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 82)
    - Davis, Richard H., 1967; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 83)
    - Day, Henry B., 1952; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 84)
    - Deacon, Charles W., 1966; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 85)
    - Demerath, N. J., 1952; 4 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 86)
    - De Palma, Samuel, 1969-1970; 3 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 87)
    - d'Harnoncourt, René, 1949; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 88)
    - Dittert, J., 1971; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 89)
    - Douglas, Mrs. Paul, 1952; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 90)
    - Dow, Edward A. Jr., 1967; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 91)
    - Draper, William H. Jr., 1969; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 92)
    - Dudley, Henry A., 1968; 5 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 93)
    - Duffus, Ursula, 1951; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 94)
    - Dulles, John Foster, 1953; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 95)
    - Dumontet, George, 1965; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 96)
    - Dunn, Frederick S., 1953; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 97)
    - Dunning, Henry W., 1953; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 98)
    - East, John, 1945; 4 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 99)
    - ECAFE (Economic Commission for Asia and the Far East), 1956-1965; 20 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 100)
    - Hammarskjold, Dag, 1957 (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 100)
    - Edelsberg, Herman, 1968; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 101)
    - Edwards, Derek, 1948-1949; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 102)
    - Edwards, Edith, 1949 (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 103)
    - Eggleston, Roger, 1969; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 104)
    - Eisenhart, L. P., 1951; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 105)
    - Eklund, Sigvard, 1965; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 106)
    - Elbrick, C. Burke, 1951; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 107)
    - Eliot, Martha M., 1957; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 108)
    - Elmandjra, Mahdi, 1971; 3 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 109)
    - Elmendorf, A. Edward, 1969-1970; 6 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 110)
    - Elsbree, Willard H. (Wid), 1953; 1966; 4 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 111)
    - Emmerich, Herbert, 1951; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 112)
    - Ende, Jean, 1953; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 113)
    - Ennals, John A. F., 1949; 1951; 4 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 114)
    - Estes, Mrs. Charles, 1950; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 115)
    - Etchats, Raymond, 1951; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 116)
    - Evans, Luther H. (Commission to Study the Organization of Peace), 1953; 1975; 3 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 117)
    - Evron, Ephraim, 1966; 3 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 118)
    - Ewing, Oscar R., 1950; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 119)
    - Fahy, Charles, 1952; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 120)
    - Fasteau, Irving J. (Jack), 1951; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 121)
    - Figgins, Dan W. Jr., 1971; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 122)
    - Figueroa, Ana, 1954; 1964; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 123)
    - Finger, Seymour M. (Max), 1965; 1970; 4 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 124)
    - Finkelstein, Lawrence S., 1949-1953; 5 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 125)
    - Fleischman, Harry, 1952; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 126)
    - Flinn, John C., 1944; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 127)
    - Flounders, Lila May Walkden, 1952; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 128)
    - Fluker, Robert J., 1965-1973; 9 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 129)
    - Fobes, Jack, 1967; 1969; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 130)
    - Folsom, Marion B., 1952; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 131)
    - Fontaine, Pierre-Michel, 1971; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 132)
    - Forster, Clifford, 1952; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 133)
    - Fredericks, J. Wayne, 1963; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 134)
    - Free, Lloyd A., 1949-1951; 4 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 135)
    - Freedgood, Sy, 1952; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 136)
    - Friiss, Finn, 1949; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 137)
    - Frumkin, Grzegorz, 1950; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 138)
    - Frye, William R., 1951; 5 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 139)
    - Fuchs, J. R., 1972; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 140)
    - Galbraith, John Kenneth, 1967; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 141)
    - Galbraith, Lynn, 1970; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 142)
    - Gardiner, Robert K. A., 1969-1971; 6 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 143)
    - Gardner, Richard N., 1965-1975; 6 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 144)
    - Georges-Picot, Guillaume, 1952; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 145)
    - Gerig, Benjamin, 1943-1945; 17 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 146)
    - Ghosh, D., 1971-1973; 18 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 147)
    - Giesecke, Albert A., 1951; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 148)
    - Glasser, Melvin A., 1950; 3 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 149)
    - Gobetz, Giles Edward, 1971; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 150)
    - Goedhard, van Heuvan, 1949; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 151)
    - Goldberg, Dorothy (Mrs. Arthur J), 1967-1968; 3 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 152)
    - Goldman, Olive Remington, 1952-1953; 4 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 153)
    - Goldschmidt, Arthur, 1966-1967; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 154)
    - Goodrich, Carter, 1951; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 155)
    - Gough, Betty C., 1971-1972; 3 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 156)
    - Gow, L. M., 1953; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 157)
    - Grace, Alonzo, 1949; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 158)
    - Graham, Pierre R., 1969; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 159)
    - Grant, Roger, 1969; 3 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 160)
    - Green, James Frederick (Jim), 1950-1966; 38 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 161)
    - Green, James Frederick (Commission to Study the Organization of Peace). Letters to Kotschnig, 1974-1978; 34 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 162)
    - Green, James Frederick. Letters to others, 1975-1977; 25 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 163)
    - Green, William, 1950; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 164)
    - Greenberg, Harry & Tania, 1952; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 165)
    - Greene, Joseph N. (Jerry), 1970; 3 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 166)
    - Greenfield, Sir Harry, 1965; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 167)
    - Greenwald, Joseph A., 1970; 5 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 168)
    - Griffith, John, 1968; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 169)
    - Gross, Nelson, 1972; 3 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 170)
    - Guenther, Kenneth A., 1969; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 171)
    - Gulick, Luther, 1943-1944; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 172)
    - Haberler, Gottfried, 1951-1952; 3 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 173)
    - Hahn, Lorena B., 1953; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 174)
    - Hall, Graham, 1955; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 175)
    - Hall, William O., 1950; 4 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 176)
    - Hammarskjold, Dag, 1953; 1955; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 177)
    - Hanes, John W. Jr., 1958; 1968; 3 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 178)
    - Hanson, Haldore (Hal), 1950; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 179)
    - Hauser, Rita E., 1969; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 180)
    - Hausmann-Kohnstann, Dinah E., 1949; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 181)
    - Havighurst, Robert, 1949; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 182)
    - Haviland, H. Field, 1950; 6 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 183)
    - Hayes, Lewis Wendell, 1953; 1956; 3 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 184)
    - Hayward, Michael, 1971-1973; 7 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 185)
    - Heath, Kathryn G., 1956; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 186)
    - Heffelfinger, Elizabeth (Brad), 1953-1969; 37 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 187)
    - Heinz, H. J., 1949; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 188)
    - Henderson, Julia, 1951-1966; 6 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 189)
    - Hendrick, James Pomeroy, 1967; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 190)
    - Hersey, Evelyn W., 1953-1954; 6 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 191)
    - Herz, Martin F., 1960-1970; 5 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 192)
    - Hessel, Stephane, 1952; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 193)
    - Hickerson, John D., 1950-1952; 3 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 194)
    - Hinton, Deane R., 1965; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 195)
    - Hoehler, Fred K., 1950; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 196)
    - Hoffman, Hallock, 1953; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 197)
    - Hoffman, Paul, 1965-1971; 6 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 198)
    - Hoffman, Thomas E., 1953; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 199)
    - Hoover, John Edgar, 1952; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 200)
    - Hoover, Lawrence H. Jr. (Harry), 1970; 5 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 201)
    - Hornick, Lillian, 1949-1972; 11 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 202)
    - Horton, Mildred McAfee, 1953; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 203)
    - Hovde, Bryn J., 1949; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 204)
    - Hruska, Roman L., 1959; 3 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 205)
    - Huber, Hermann, 1953; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 206)
    - Hull, Cordell, 1939; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 207)
    - Hull, Spahr, 1950; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 208)
    - Humphrey, Hubert H., 1957-1967; 6 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 209)
    - Hutchins, Robert M., 1952; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 210)
    - Huttrer, Charles P., 1966; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 211)
    - Idenburg, Philip J., 1950; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 212)
    - Ingersoll, John, 1970; 1972; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 213)
    - Institute of Inter-American Affairs, 1951; 3 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 214)
    - The International Platform Association, 1965; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 215)
    - Jackson, Elmore, 1966; 1971; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 216)
    - Jackson, Sir Robert, 1969; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 217)
    - Jacobs, George, 1970; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 218)
    - Jacobson, Harold Karan, 1968; 1970; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 219)
    - Jenks, C. Wilfred, 1952-1970; 4 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 220)
    - Johnson, Brian, 1970; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 221)
    - Johnson, G. Griffith, 1970; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 222)
    - Johnson, Joseph E., 1968-1970; 5 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 223)
    - Johnston, William D. Jr., 1966; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 224)
    - Jolles, Paul, 1964-1967; 7 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 225)
    - Jones, David DeL, 1942; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 226)
    - Jones, G. Paul Jr., 1970; 3 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 227)
    - Judd, Charles S. (League of Nations Union), 1937-1946; 15 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 228)
    - Kabul (consulting trip, RGA Ministry of Planning), 1959; 14 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 229)
    - Kain, Joan, 1950; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 230)
    - Kaufmann, Johan, 1966; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 231)
    - Kayser, Jacques, 1949; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 232)
    - Kelakos, Michael G., 1970; 3 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 233)
    - Keller, Adolphe, 1952; 3 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 234)
    - Kellermann, Henry J., 1949-1966; 7 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 235)
    - Kenyon, Dorothy, 1949; 3 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 236)
    - Kerr, Malcolm, 1969; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 237)
    - Khan, Mir, 1968-1969; 5 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 238)
    - Khan, Prince Sadruddin Aga, 1971; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 239)
    - Kiefer, Alexander, 1966; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 240)
    - Killick, John E., 1967; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 241)
    - Kirkova, Tatiana E., 1973-1975; 12 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 242)
    - Kironde, Apollo K., 1970; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 243)
    - Kittani, Ismat T., 1970-1971; 4 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 244)
    - Klutznick, Philip M., 1966-1972; 9 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 245)
    - Knepper, Alvin, 1952; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 246)
    - Koffka, Elisabeth, 1950; 4 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 247)
    - Kohler, Foy D., 1952; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 248)
    - Kohn, Vera Sharpe, 1953; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 249)
    - Korey, William, 1965-1966; 4 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 250)
    - Kovach, John, 1952; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 251)
    - Kripp, Joseph B., 1951; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 252)
    - Krould, Harry J., 1950; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 253)
    - Kuševic, Vladimir, 1968-1972; 13 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 254)
    - Labouisse, Henry R., 1971; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 255)
    - Lacey, John A., 1965; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 256)
    - Laise, Carol C., 1972; 2 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 257)
    - Lall, K. B., 1965; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 258)
    - Lally, Dorothy, 1966; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 259)
    - Landon, Kenneth P., 1973; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 260)
    - Laugier, Henri, 1950-1968; 12 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 261)
    - Laves, Walter H. C., 1951-1966; 8 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 262)
    - Leddy, John M., 1949-1965; 3 items (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 263)
    - Leetsma, Robert, 1970; 1 item (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 264)